Welcome to your first project.
مرحبًا بكم في مشروعكم الأول.
Global temperature has been a hot topic in recent years,
لقد كانت درجة الحرارة العالمية موضوعًا مهمًا في الأعوام الأخيرة،
as politicians argue over climate change policy,
حيث يتجادل السياسيون بشأن سياسة تغير المناخ،
and scientists try to understand how the world's climate is actually changing.
ويحاول العلماء فهم كيفية تغير مناخ العالم فعليًا.
Temperature data around the world is an important part of this conversation.
بيانات درجات الحرارة حول العالم هي جزء مهم في هذه المحادثة.
To measure temperature data,
لقياس بيانات درجة الحرارة،
scientists combine measurements from the air and ocean surface.
يجمع العلماء القياسات من الهواء وسطح المحيطات.
This data is collected by weather stations on land and in the ocean.
جمعت محطات الأرصاد الجوية الموجودة على سطح الأرض وفي المحيطات هذه البيانات.
In this project, you'll analyze local and global temperature data and
في هذا المشروع، ستحللون بيانات درجات الحرارة المحلية والعالمية
compare the temperature trends where you live to overall global temperature trends.
وتقارنون اتجاهات درجات الحرارة التي تعيشون فيها مع اتجاهات درجات الحرارة العالمية العامة.
You'll analyze the data, create a data visualization and write up your findings.
ستحللون البيانات، وتنشؤون عرض البيانات وتكتبون نتائجكم.